BATUHAN ERDİN



Contact

Phone

0507 683 13 62

Email

erdin.batu478@gmail.com

Linkedin

https://www.linkedin.com/in/batuhanerdin/

Education

ULUDAG UNIVERSITY

2020-2024 Computer Engineering

Language

English

Programming Languages

- Unity
- C#
- Python
- . C
- lava
- C++

About

I was born in 2002 in Balıkesir. I am a third-year Computer Engineering Student at Uludag University.

I am very passionate about game development. I have been developing games using Unity for approximately 3 years starting from the end of high school And I'm working on coding mostly with C#.

Skills

- Unity
- Object Oriented Programming
- Visual Studio Code/Community
- Photoshop
- HTML
- CSS

- Oracle
- SQL
- Virtual Box
- Microsoft Office Programs
- İntelliJ İde

Work experience

Robotics Automation Society
VICE-CHAIRMAN OF RAS in IEEE Bursa Uludag University
Student Branch for 1 year .

Peilabs LLC

Intern Game Developer

Bursa - July,2023 - August,2023

Peilabs LLC

Part - Time Game Developer

Bursa - August, 2023 - Present

Achievements

Harmonia Games - Kargakarga Gamejam
 2nd Place Award